{
    "subject": "resource/Mrs_Henderson_Presents",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Mrs. Henderson Presents is British films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9832905530929565,
            "question": "Is 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' a British film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9402871131896973,
            "question": "How is 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' representative of British cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791471719741821,
            "question": "What type of films is 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7613481283187866,
            "question": "Are there any famous British actors in 'Mrs. Henderson Presents'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7542318105697632,
            "question": "What country are the films in 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6768203377723694,
            "question": "What other films might be similar to 'Mrs. Henderson Presents'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6323372721672058,
            "question": "What is the setting of 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37224850058555603,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in British films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3404349386692047,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a British film genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24477289617061615,
            "question": "What impact have British films had on the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Mrs. Henderson Presents is British films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7922_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a British film genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7922_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in British films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7922_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the setting of 'Mrs. Henderson Presents' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7922_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7922_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate any more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Mrs Henderson Presents\" and its setting, confirming that it is a British film. Therefore, the statement \"The subject of Mrs. Henderson Presents is British films\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}